So, look, forget about this FBA nonsense.
And also here in Africa, we have tribalists who believe that you guys in America are not part of us.
Both sides. Both sides have divisive people who don't want to accept each other.
Forget about this nonsense. We are all Africans, whether you like it or not.
We are Africans. We are Africans.
Africans, there is, look, I always ask these FBA people one question.
Fine. You want to be a distinct group and you want to be independent.
Yes. Fine. Well, let me ask you a question then.
Has white supremacy, you know, white supremacy is a global institution.
Yes. How can you defeat a global institution on your own as FBA people?
White supremacy is conjoined. White supremacy in America is conjoined with the Vatican, is conjoined with the IMF, with the European Union, with the whole UN, with the whole World Bank.
And you are there as FBA is thinking that you'll defeat white supremacy alone.
It's either you're dumb or ignorant or both at the same time.
Or your goal isn't to defeat white supremacy at all.
Exactly. Or your goal is just to remain and to survive and to thrive in white supremacy, which is impossible.
Badam, badam, badam, badam, badam.
Badam, badam, badam.